《生化危机：惩罚》
我叫爱丽丝
My name is Alice.
曾为保护伞公司工作
I worked for the Umbrella Corporation,
那是全世界最强大的商业实体
the largest and most powerful commercial entity in the world.
我曾在称作蜂巢的某秘密科研所负责安保工作
I was head of security at a secret high-tech facility called the Hive,
这是一个开发生化武器的大型地下实验室
a giant underground laboratory developing experimental, viral weaponry.
但出了事故
There was an incident.
病毒外逸
A virus escaped.
死了很多人
A lot of people died.
可问题是…他们还没死透
The trouble was, they didn't stay dead.
控制蜂巢的计算机具备最尖端的人工智能
The computer that controlled the Hive was a state-of-the-art artificial intelligence:
她叫红后
The Red Queen.
红后对病毒的扩散做出了极端应对
The Red Queen responded to the threat of the viral outbreak in an extreme way.
她大开杀戒
She went homicidal.
- 你们全得死在里面 - 红后要杀死每一个人
- You're all going to die down here. - The Red Queen attempted to kill everyone!
不论是否感染
Whether they were infected or not.
我成功逃脱 但事情远未结束
I managed to escape, but this was only the beginning.
病毒如野火般迅速传播
Viral outbreaks spread like wildfire,
先是横扫美国 接着是全世界…
first across the United States, then the world.
然而 T病毒不仅能让死人复生
The T-Virus didn't just bring the dead back to life.
还使其恐怖地变异
It mutated them in terrifying ways.
除了天启之外
Despite the apocalypse they had created,
保护伞公司还实验了其它致命病毒
the Umbrella Corporation continued to experiment with the deadly virus.
我也被感染
I was infected.
但病毒却从细胞层面与我结合
But the virus bonded with me on a cellular level.
我拥有了超能力
I developed powers.
你的遗传结构就是关键
Your genetic structure is the key.
变得与众不同
I became different.
所向披靡
Powerful.
势不可挡
Unstoppable.
我愈加强大 人类却日渐孱弱
As I got stronger, the human race became weaker.
我尽力把幸存者带到安全地点
I tried my best to lead what survivors I could find to safety,
但我们却被无情追杀
but we were pursued relentlessly.
连我的朋友吉尔·瓦伦丁也被保护伞抓住洗脑
Even my friend Jill Valentine was seized and brainwashed by Umbrella.
下令射杀
Shoot to kill.
最终 我遭遇保护伞公司掌门人
Finally, I confronted the head of the Umbrella Corporation,
阿尔伯特·威斯克
Albert Wesker.
他夺走了我的超能力 但我依然将其击败
He robbed me of my powers, but I still managed to defeat him.
最后 我们以为一切都已结束
At last, we thought it was over.
以为我们已经逃离劫难
We thought we had survived the horror.
结果我们错了
But we were wrong.
我们仍需为求生而战
Once again, we found ourselves fighting for our lives.
快快快
Go, go, go!
快起床啦 宝贝 我们晚了
Rise and shine. Come on, babe. We're late.
闹钟没响
The alarm didn't go off.
贝姬还没起床
Becky's not up yet.
安德森老师肯定要生气
Miss Henderson's gonna be pissed.
你也知道 送她上学迟到会怎样
You know how they get when you drop her off late at the school.
宝贝 你还好吗？
Babe? You all right, babe?
没事
Yeah.
我去叫贝姬
I'll go get Becky.
我帮你充了电
I charged your batteries for you.
贝姬 你也知道安德森老师…
Becky, you know Miss Henderson,
希望你边打手语边说出声来
she wants you to speak while you sign.
谢谢爸爸
Thank you, Daddy.
等你从学校回来 我给你个惊喜
When you come back from school, I have a surprise for you.
我听到啦
I heard that.
电池越来越不经用了
These batteries are lasting less and less.
得买些新的
We need to get some new ones.
- 我可以回家时带几块 - 我又要迟到了
- I can pick some up on my way home. - I'm gonna be late again.
该死
Aw, shit.
我去睡房帮你再找件衬衫
I'll get you another shirt from the bedroom.
昨天有人帮你取干洗了哦
Someone picked up your dry-cleaning yesterday.
你可真是我的小天使
You are my little angel, aren't you?
你不是要迟到了吗？
You're gonna be late, remember?
对
Yeah.
我去帮你拿衬衫
Heh. I'll get you that shirt.
保护贝姬
Get Becky back! Aah!
不
No!
救命 救命
Help! Help us!
快 快
Come on. Come on!
快
Come on.
快走
Go.
快跑
Go!
不
No!
- 退后 - 等等
- Back! - Wait!
- 等等 - 别过来
- Wait! - Stay back!
你脑子有毛病啊？
What is wrong with you?
快点上车
Come on, get in.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
你问我 我问谁
Your guess is as good as mine.
这些人怎么这样啊？
Why are these people doing this?
它们不能叫人了 不是人了
Those things are not people. Not any…
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
还能动吗？好样的
Can you move? Okay.
快点
Come on.
妈的
Shit!
妈妈
Mommy.
妈妈 快点
Mommy, come on.
快跑
Go!
我爱你
I love you.
生化人爱丽丝
Project Alice,
你为什么背叛公司？
why did you turn against Umbrella?
吉尔？
Jill?
是你吗？
Is that you?
生化人爱丽丝
Project Alice,
你为什么背叛公司？
why did you turn against Umbrella?
克里斯和克莱尔怎么了？
What happened to Chris and Claire?
船上其他人呢？
Where are the others from the ship?
生化人爱丽丝
Project Alice,
你为谁工作？
who do you work for?
生化人爱丽丝
Project Alice,
你为谁工作？
who do you work for?
吉尔 你为什么这么做？
Jill, why are you doing this?
警告 警告
Warning. Warning.
非法计算机入侵
Unauthorized computer access.
安全系统失效
Security system disabled.
中央计算机2分钟后重启
Central computer reboot in two minutes.
安全系统失效
Security system disabled.
中央计算机1分50秒后重启
Central computer reboot in one minute, 50 seconds.
安全系统失效
Security system disabled.
中央计算机1分40秒后重启
Central computer reboot in one minute 40 seconds.
安全系统失效
Security system disabled.
中央计算机30秒后重启
Central computer reboot in 30 seconds.
安全系统失效
Security system disabled.
中央计算机20秒后重启
Central computer reboot in 20 seconds.
安全系统失效
Security system disabled.
中央计算机10秒后重启
Central computer reboot in 10 seconds.
中央计算机重启中
Central computer rebooting.
安保全体集合
Scramble all security teams.
镭射网刀清除走廊
And sweep the corridor with the laser grid.
已就绪
Stand by.
东京序列启动
Tokyo sequence initialized.
已就绪
Stand by.
欢迎进入保护伞控制中心
Welcome to Umbrella Central Control.
这才对嘛
Yeah.
别动
Don't.
- 我叫… - 艾达·王
- My name is… - Ada Wong.
保护伞公司特勤人员 威斯克手下明星特工
Operative for the Umbrella Corporation, one of Albert Wesker's top agents.
你的底细我清楚
I know exactly who and what you are.
现在最大的问题是
Now, the real question is:
为什么我不立刻杀了你？
Why don't I just cancel your contract right now?
我不再为保护伞工作了
I don't work for Umbrella anymore,
阿尔伯特·威斯克也一样
and neither does Albert Wesker.
我才不管
I don't care.
你可以杀了她
You can kill her if you like,
但真相也将石沉大海
but then you'll never get out of this place.
- 威斯克 - 现在乖一点
- Wesker. - Now, be a good girl.
把刀放下
Put down the knife.
爱丽丝
And Alice,
真高兴见到你
how nice to see you again.
她怎么逃的？
How did she get out?
显然有帮手
She's obviously getting help.
肯定有内奸
We have a traitor in this facility.
小姐 安全系统关闭了2分钟
Security systems were shut down for two minutes.
- 控制中心呢？ - 无法唤醒
- What about Control? - We still can't raise them.
控制中心所有人均已被我杀死
I executed everyone in this control room.
我让威斯克黑掉主机
I enabled Wesker to hack the mainframe.
关闭了安全系统
We shut down the security systems.
帮你逃出羁押室
We let you out of that cell.
我们要设法让你离开这里
We have to get you out of this facility.
- 你们为什么要帮我？ - 我们需要你
- So why do you want to help me? - We need you.
人类濒于灭绝
The human race faces extinction.
合作是我们最后一线生机
Our only hope of survival is for us to work together.
我绝不离开
I'm not going anywhere
直到弄清这是哪里 这里发生了什么事
until I know where we are and what the hell is going on here.
你在保护伞的核心实验基地
You're in the Prime Umbrella testing facility.
东京是怎么回事
Explain Tokyo.
你看到的只不过是个逼真复制
What you saw was just a detailed re-creation, nothing more.
也就几个街区
It goes on for a few city blocks. That's all.
可我在室外
I was outside.
是吗？
Were you?
看到天空了吗？
Saw the sky, did you?
- 当时是晚上 - 星星呢？月亮呢？
- It was night. - Stars? The moon?
实验平台高300英尺 天花板是黑色的
The testing floor is 300 feet high, the ceiling black.
所以总是晚上
It's usually night in there.
僵尸不就喜欢晚上出来吗？
But isn't that when the monsters come out anyway?
- 当时在下雨 - 气候控制
- It was raining. - Climate control.
风 雨
Wind, rain.
下点雪也未尝不可
They can even make it snow if they want to.
- 为什么造这个地方？ - 很简单
- Why build such a place? - Simple.
保护伞公司的核心利润
The Umbrella Corporation derived its primary income
来自于生化武器销售
from the sale of viral weaponry,
而这无法在真实世界测试
something that's impossible to test in the real world.
他们复制了纽约市中心
They re-created the center of New York,
模拟病毒爆发 向俄方买家演示
simulated an outbreak, showed it to the Russians,
出售其病毒
and sold them the virus.
同样 他们模拟莫斯科病毒爆发 然后卖给美国人
They simulated an outbreak in Moscow, sold it to the Americans.
还有东京的爆发
An outbreak in Tokyo.
然后卖给中国人
Sold it to the Chinese.
- 再演示中国的爆发 - 然后卖给日本人
- An outbreak in China. - Sold it to the Japanese.
没错 所以各国都得购买
Exactly. Everyone had to have it.
保护伞公司引发了新一轮军备竞赛
The Umbrella Corporation built a new arms race.
只是这次生化武器取代了核武器
Only, this time, it was biological rather than nuclear.
暴利经营
Highly profitable.
这就是一切的源头
And this is where it all happened.
这里是保护伞公司的杰作
This is Umbrella's greatest creation.
也是最险峻的要害命门
The belly of the beast.
那我们还不离开这个鬼地方？
So why don't we just get the hell out of here?
等等
Stop.
日出不到一分钟了
Sunup is in less than a minute.
你自己来看看吧
Why don't you just see for yourself?
这个基地位于俄罗斯北部
This facility is located in the straits of Kamchatka,
堪察加峡湾 八十年代
northern Russia. The old Soviet Union
前苏联曾在此建有潜艇船坞
built submarine pens here in the '80s.
冷战结束后
After the Cold War ended,
保护伞公司将其扩建为实验平台
the Umbrella Corporation expanded them, and built the testing floor.
从未有人从这里逃走
No one has ever escaped from this facility.
冰壳
Ice.
你得尽量寻求帮助
You'll need all the help you can get,
所以我准备了一支突击队从地面进入基地协助你
so I've arranged for a strike team to enter from the surface and assist you.
那里就是保护伞实验基地的入风口
There they are. Intake vents for the Umbrella facility.
像是已经废弃
Looks abandoned.
他们就希望别人这么想
That's what they want you to think.
走吧 我们只有2小时来救出爱丽丝和艾达
Let's move. We have just two hours to extract Alice and Ada.
否则便可能遭遇保护伞重火力后援部队
After that, we can expect heavy Umbrella reinforcements.
开启旁路模式
Running a bypass.
这是艾达给我们的进入密码
These are the codes from Ada.
你相信她吗？
Do you trust her?
输入就是了
Just enter the numbers.
爆炸量设置完毕
The charges are set.
进去了
We're in.
大干一场吧
Let's go do this.
他们来了
They're in.
突击队驻守了一部升降机 确保你们能逃上地面
The strike team has secured an elevator for your escape to the surface.
他们会消灭保护伞的抵抗力量
They will eliminate Umbrella resistance,
然后与我们会合
then rendezvous with us,
护送我们出去
and escort us out.
你有个朋友也在里面
They have a friend of yours with them.
卢瑟·韦斯特
Luther West.
他还活着吗？
He's alive?
抓紧了 女士们
All right. Hold on, ladies.
对表 两小时计时
Synchronize watches. Two hours exactly in
3 2 1 开始
three, two, one, mark.
里昂
Leon,
为什么不用遥控引爆？
why don't we trigger remotely?
防止对方信号干扰
Can't risk them jamming the signal.
不论我们成功与否 都要炸毁这里
And whether we succeed or not, this facility has to be destroyed.
如果两小时搞不定怎么办？
What if we take longer than two hours?
那你最好很能憋气
Then I hope you're really good at holding your breath.
安保主管瓦伦丁已到达东京测试环境
Security Chief Valentine has reached the Tokyo test environment.
她是来抓你的
She's tracking you.
他们朝这里来了
They're headed this way.
她的命令是能抓就抓
Her orders are to recapture you, if possible,
抓不到就杀
terminate you if necessary.
谁下的命令？
Who's giving these orders?
红后
The Red Queen.
- 那台计算机吗？ - 对
- The computer? - Yes.
就是蜂巢那种人工智能机
The same artificial intelligence you encountered in the Hive.
现在她控制了保护伞公司的余孽
She now controls what remains of the Umbrella Corporation.
绝不会放你逃出这里
She will stop at nothing to prevent you escaping to the surface.
我绘制了一幅逃生线路图
I've plotted an escape route for you.
你们穿过纽约测试环境
You'll cross the New York environment to Suburbia
在郊区与突击队会合
where you'll rendezvous with the strike team.
他们会护送你们穿过莫斯科实验环境
They'll escort you through the Moscow environment,
直达潜艇船坞
to the submarine pens.
然后乘升降机回到地面
And take the elevator back to the surface.
红后已开始截获信号
The Red Queen has intercepted my signal.
马上会夺回基地控制权
She's about to regain control of this facility.
你们要快 我不能再…
You must hurry. I can't…
别听背叛者威斯克的
Don't listen to the traitor Wesker.
现在由我掌控
I am in control now.
生化人爱丽丝 艾达·王
Project Alice, Ada Wong,
待着别动
stay where you are.
- 行动 - 生化人爱丽丝
- Let's move. - Project Alice,
你们都会死在这里
you're all going to die down here.
早听你说过了
I've heard that before.
防御队形
Defensive formation.
锁定目标
Mark your targets.
随时开火
Fire at will.
前方就是潜艇船坞
Submarine pens are up ahead.
巴里 你我当前锋
Barry, you and I take point.
30分钟后与爱丽丝和艾达会合
We rendezvous with Alice and Ada in 30 minutes.
安全
Clear.
那可是个大家伙
Now, that's some hardware.
台风级的
Typhoon class.
苏俄迄今最大的核潜艇
The biggest nuclear subs the Soviets ever built.
保护伞用它向世界各地私运生化武器
Umbrella used them to secretly transport bioweapons all over the globe.
我们得快点 只有不到90分钟了
Let's pick up the pace. We have less than 90 minutes.
发现入侵者
Intruders detected.
锁定目标将其消灭
Targeted for termination.
纽约
New York.
逃生还要再通过两个测试环境
We need to cross two more test environments to escape.
行动吧
Let's move.
保护伞为什么还做这些测试？
Why would Umbrella continue to run these tests?
他们想研究生化危机 想知道怎么控制它
They want to study the biohazard, learn how to control it.
启动纽约序列
Initialize New York sequence.
激活生化危机
Activate biohazard.
已就绪 已就绪
Stand by. Stand by.
纽约序列启动
New York sequence initialized.
红后
The Red Queen.
她要激活生化武器阻止我们 行动吧
She's activating bioweapons to stop us. Let's go.
等等
Wait.
你听到了吗？
You hear that?
知道是什么吗？
You know what it is?
我有个主意
I have an idea.
开什么玩笑
You have got to be kidding me.
傻大个
Hey, boys.
这办法够狠
Bad idea.
走吧
Let's move.
我们比计划晚了
We're behind schedule.
什么情况？
What's going on?
模拟序列已结束
It's the end of the sequence.
很少能超过一小时
They rarely last more than an hour.
走吧
Come on.
趁红后还没激活其它武器
Before the Red Queen activates something else.
目标存活
Targets survived.
安保主管瓦伦丁负责拦截
Security Chief Valentine to intercept.
入侵者进入莫斯科测试环境
Intruders entering Moscow test environment.
激活不死者罗斯·普拉格斯
Activate Las Plagas Undead.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
红后知道我们在这里 提高警惕
The Red Queen knows we're here. Keep your eyes open.
已就绪 已就绪
Stand by. Stand by.
莫斯科序列启动
Moscow sequence initialized.
- 怎么了？ - 听
- What? - Listen.
在那边
Right there.
这是什么鬼东西？
What the hell are those things?
后撤 全部后撤
Fall back. Everyone fall back.
是云吗？
Clouds.
假的
They're not real.
是全息投影
It's a holographic projection.
运行模拟影像时
When they were running a simulation,
没有人会朝天上看 相信我吧
trust me, no one was looking at the sky.
这是会合地点
This is the rendezvous point.
突击队来晚了
The strike team is late.
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
你背后房子有人
There's movement in the house behind you.
上面的窗子
Upstairs window.
他们怎么在这里？
Why would they be in here?
借用我的克隆体
They're using clones of me.
当然
Of course.
你是50个基础样本之一
You were one of the 50 basic models.
基础样本
"Basic models."
不然保护伞怎么在测试场景安插居民呢？
How do you think Umbrella populates these test scenarios?
每次模拟演示都要死好几百人
Hundreds of people dead each time they run a simulation.
保护伞向他们植入一些基础记忆
Umbrella imprints them with basic memories,
刚够其对生化危机做出正常情绪反应
just enough to ensure a correct emotional response to the threat of the biohazard.
这次测试她可能是个郊区家庭主妇
In one life, she could be a suburban housewife.
下次就可能是纽约的商人
The next, a businesswoman in New York.
再下次又可能是保护伞的打手
The next, a soldier working for Umbrella.
妈妈
Mommy.
我按你说的藏起来了
I hid like you told me.
你衣服和发型怎么变了？
What happened to your clothes and your hair?
火箭弹 卧倒
RPG! Down!
我们快没时间了
We're running out of time!
你得赶紧找条突围路线
You have to find us a way out now!
马上
Almost there!
这都是假的
None of this is real.
- 可对她是真的 - 这个我理解
- It is to her. - I know. That's the point.
她对你的所有感情都是植入的
All these feelings she has for you, they were imprinted.
一天前 她还是白纸一张
A day ago, she was a blank slate.
冷库里我可以给你找到一打的她
I could show you a dozen just like her in cold storage.
对不起 但这是事实
I'm sorry, but it's true.
准备好了
Ready.
我很快吧？
I was fast, wasn't I?
是的
Yes, you were.
- 爸爸 - 他不是你爸爸
- Daddy? - He's not your father.
能抓就抓
Capture if possible.
不行就杀掉
Terminate if necessary.
这里可有孩子
There's a child here.
那是你的事 与我们无关
Your problem, not ours.
心如铁石 你一点也没变
All heart. You haven't changed a bit.
我不认识你
I don't know you, lady.
不投降就去死
Now, surrender or die.
蹲下
Stay down!
- B组冲上去 - 好的 长官
- Advance in teams! - Yes, ma'am!
你不能待在这里
You can't stay here!
这个会告诉你怎么出去
This will show you the way out.
穿过莫斯科 去潜艇船坞
Go through Moscow to the submarine pens.
拿着
Take this.
我最好轻装上阵
The less I have with me, the better.
A组推进
Alpha Team forward!
他们来了 我们得快点
They're coming. Hurry.
快跑
Go.
找到路了
I've got it!
这边
This way!
嘿
Hey.
等等
Wait.
她帮过我们 记得吗？
She helped us. Remember?
你俩没死
You two made it!
我以为自己是唯一的幸存者
Thought I was the only one that survived.
这是哪儿？怎么都标的俄语？
What is this place, and why is everything in Russian?
你这副性虐装扮又是怎么回事？
And what's with the S & M getup?
- 你知道怎么用吗？ - 我支持禁枪的
- You know how to use this? - I campaigned for gun control.
你不明白 我还抗议过美国枪械协会
No, I don't think you understand. I marched against the NRA.
听好了
Concentrate.
这就像个相机
It's just like a camera.
瞄准 射击
Point and shoot.
恭喜 你正式成为坏人了
Congratulations. You're officially a badass.
发生什么事了？
What the hell's going on here?
等我回来解释
I'll explain when I get back.
现在你要保障她的安全
You have to keep her safe.
- 你跟紧她 - 你要走？
- You stay with her. - You're going?
不是说不离开我吗？
You said you wouldn't leave.
相信我 我不会骗你
Trust me, okay? What I say is true.
肯定回来接你
I'll come back for you.
你发誓
You promise?
相信我
Trust me.
我爱你
I love you.
来吧
Come on.
她会回来的
She'll be back for you.
先找个地方藏起来
Gotta find a hiding place.
- 我遇到你姐姐了 - 什么？
- I met your sister. - What?
她人不太好
She's not very nice.
我们藏下边去
Let's try hiding down here.
这边
This way.
行动吧
Let's move!
我们也许能绕过…
We can work our way…
还等我发邀请函吗？
Waiting for a written invitation?
技术不错
Sweet ride.
当然了 这是莫斯科
Well, this is Moscow.
我听到了枪声 猜你们需要帮助
Heard gunfire. Thought you might need some help.
艾达在哪儿？
Where's Ada?
应该死了
I don't think she made it.
- 对不起 - 你看到她死了吗？
- I'm sorry. - You saw her die?
没有
No.
她总有办法
She always has a plan.
哥几个 动动手呗
Boys, you mind?
- 那打吧 - 乐意之至
- Shall we? - My pleasure.
下次再这么干 请先吱一声
Let me know when you plan on doing that again.
当心了
Heads up.
我们的小朋友又来了
Our little friend is back!
妈的
Shit.
- 快到了 - 不
- Almost there. - No.
慢点 你要干什么？
Wait. You're not going down there!
大家都没事吧？
Everyone okay?
还行
Yeah.
好 我们走
All right, let's go.
喂？
Hello?
你们出来吧
You can come out.
我回来了
I'm back.
你在哪儿找到这几位的？
Where'd you find these guys?
你是…？
Who's this?
我叫贝姬
I'm Becky.
你好 贝姬
Hi, Becky.
这是我妈妈
This is my mom.
- 你妈妈？ - 说来话长
- Your mom? Mm. - Long story.
还有22分钟
Twenty-two minutes left.
来的路没法走了
There's no going back the way we came.
对 跟那帮谢尔盖打时把地图丢了
Yeah. We lost our map with Sergei.
我有办法
I'm on it.
我们可以走这条地道
We can take this tunnel.
尽头有个竖井直通潜艇船坞
There's a service shaft that leads down to the submarine pens.
我们走
Let's go.
你怎么不给威斯克干了？
How'd you end up working for Wesker?
我不为他工作
I don't work for him,
上面情况有变
but things on the surface have changed.
威斯克说你熟悉一样武器
Wesker said you knew of some weapon,
某种能让我们扭转局势的东西
something that could turn the tide for us.
但我不可能为一个人冒那么大风险
But I don't think I would have risked so much for one person.
算你判断正确
You're probably right.
这边走
This way.
潜艇船坞就在我们上面
The submarine pens are up above us.
跟紧点
Come on. Move.
升降机平台就在前面
The elevator platforms are up ahead.
还剩11分钟
Eleven minutes.
- 我们来得及 - 等等
- We're gonna be okay. - Hold on.
- 还剩11分钟 - 我们来得及
- Eleven minutes. - We're gonna be okay.
- 等等 - 接入电力网
- Hold on. - Accessing power grid.
安排生化危机
Dispatching biohazard.
大家快登艇
Everybody get on board.
各位请扶好 下一站是男装及体育用品商店
Hold on. Next stop, menswear and sporting goods.
蹲下
Move down!
- 巴里 怎么回事？ - 我不知道
- Barry, what is it? - I don't know.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
定是有人远程切断了电源
Somebody must've cut the power remotely.
坚强些
Be strong.
我会保护你
I'm gonna keep you safe.
能在线重连吗？
Can you get it online?
没密码可不行
Not without the access codes.
9分钟 看来要选备用方案了
Nine minutes. Looks like we're going with plan B.
什么？
What?
那些爆炸物不是随便安置的
There's a reason we planted those explosives.
不
No!
妈妈
Mommy!
Aah! Mommy!
我不行了
I feel like shit.
她死定了
She's dead.
- 你干什么？ - 她还活着
- What are you doing? - She's alive.
我要去救她
I'm going to get her.
我从没失去过这么多朋友
I didn't lose friends
- 你就这么走了 - 我会回来的
- so you could walk away. - I plan on coming back.
别这样
Don't do this.
你比她重要多了
You're more important than she is.
你这就错了
That's where you're wrong.
这样真不行
This is a mistake.
请让开
Get out of my way.
我回来前别走 好吗？
Don't leave without me, okay?
开什么玩笑？我跟你一起去
Are you kidding me? I'm going with you.
别动 别动
Don't move. Don't move.
没事
It's okay.
去找孩子
Go get her back.
就喜欢挨枪子儿吗？
You like that? Huh?
前进
Move up!
回升降机
Fall back to the elevator!
你先去
You go!
我再撑会儿
I'm gonna stay a while.
巴里
Barry.
等倒计时归零
When the countdown gets down to zero,
你必须进到升降机里
you have to be on that elevator!
里昂 得有人守在这里
Someone's got to stay.Leon.
再说
Besides,
这会儿我杀得正爽
I'm kind of enjoying myself!
快 快走
Go. Go!
快
Come on!
贝姬 贝姬
Becky. Becky.
快跑
Go!
带俘虏出来
Bring out the prisoner!
敢开枪 我就杀了她
Cease your firing. Or I'll execute her.
放下枪 走出来
Now, throw down your guns, and step out.
不出来她就死定了
Step out, or she dies!
妈妈 她们是谁啊？
Mommy, who are they?
妈妈 他们是谁？
Mommy, Who are they?
妈妈 那是你吗？
Mommy, is that you?
你才是我妈妈 对吧？
You're my mommy, aren't you?
是的
I am now.
快跑
Move!
直升机正赶过来
Choppers are on their way,
都好好喘口气吧
so just sit back and relax.
怎么了？
What's going on?
那是什么？
What the hell is that?
贝姬 你受伤了吗？
Becky, are you hurt?
没有
No. I'm okay.
跟你说她有办法的
Told you she'd have a plan.
只有你们两个？
Only the two of you?
两个就够了
It'll be enough.
罗斯·普拉格斯的寄生体
The Las Plagas parasite.
消灭生化人爱丽丝
Terminate Project Alice.
爱丽丝
Alice!
你杀不死我
You can't kill me.
我不需要杀你
I don't need to.
我要杀了你
I'm coming for you!
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
里昂
Leon.
那是什么？
What is it?
援兵
It's help.
你苏醒了真好
Glad to have you back.
我不管
I don't care.
威斯克
Wesker.
你倒悠闲自在
I see you've made yourself at home.
没错 我是挺放松的
Well, I must say, it does have a certain ease to it.
这是什么？你给我注射了什么？
What is this? What have you done to me?
你曾是唯一与T病毒成功结合的人
You were the only one to successfully bond with the T-Virus,
为了发挥她的最大威力
to fully realize her powers.
现在我需要你
Well, now I have need of you.
以前的你
The old you.
所以把超能力还给你
So I've given you back your gift.
你就是武器
You are the weapon.
- 我要杀了你 - 也许
- I'm gonna kill you. - Perhaps.
但首先你得完成任务
But first, you have work to do.
红后要毁灭地球上所有生命
The Red Queen is determined to destroy all life on earth.
这是我们人类仅存的生命
This is the last that remain of us, of the human race.
我们似乎应该同仇敌忾
It seems we're bonded against a common foe.
这就是要你回来的原因 成为终极武器
This is why we needed you back. The ultimate weapon.
这是人类的背水之战
This is humanity's last stand.
终结的起始
The beginning of the end.